<DOC> <DOCNO> 1 </DOCNO> Home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 2 </DOCNO> Why the pandemic is causing spikes in break-ups and divorces - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 3 </DOCNO> Why it's hard for people of colour to be themselves at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 4 </DOCNO> Why Indian wedding traditions could trump the pandemic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 5 </DOCNO> How '15-minute cities' will change the way we socialise - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 6 </DOCNO> How Covid-19 is changing women’s lives - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 7 </DOCNO> Can reality TV shows help lead the way for inclusivity? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 8 </DOCNO> Why getting a name right matters - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 9 </DOCNO> Cultural Traditions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 10 </DOCNO> Sweden’s male-only supper clubs...for feminists - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 11 </DOCNO> Will online degrees become more ‘legitimate’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 12 </DOCNO> Why you’re more creative in coffee shops - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 13 </DOCNO> Why 'Dinner Table Syndrome' is getting worse for deaf people - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 14 </DOCNO> Gender - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 15 </DOCNO> Why imposter syndrome hits women and women of colour harder - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 16 </DOCNO> Why some Chinese believe a name change could improve luck - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 17 </DOCNO> How social-distancing symbols are changing our cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 18 </DOCNO> The ‘flow state’: Where creative work thrives - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 19 </DOCNO> The reason Zoom calls drain your energy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 20 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: The possible long-term mental health impacts - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 21 </DOCNO> Psychology - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 22 </DOCNO> How microaggressions cause lasting pain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 23 </DOCNO> How corporate diversity initiatives trap workers of colour - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 24 </DOCNO> The docility myth flattening Asian women’s careers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 25 </DOCNO> Why reskilling won’t always guarantee you a new job - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 26 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Why dating feels so different now - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 27 </DOCNO> Why do women still change their names? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 28 </DOCNO> Why our reliance on cars could start booming - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 29 </DOCNO> Inequality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 30 </DOCNO> How bike-friendly ‘slow streets' are changing cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 31 </DOCNO> Diversity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 32 </DOCNO> Beyond the 9-to-5 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 33 </DOCNO> Relationships - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 34 </DOCNO> Could the Swedish lifestyle help fight coronavirus? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 35 </DOCNO> The challenge of a job that doesn't meet your needs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 36 </DOCNO> Working from home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 37 </DOCNO> Conflict - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 38 </DOCNO> Public Transport - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 39 </DOCNO> Two-Metre Economy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 40 </DOCNO> What outdoor space tells us about inequality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 41 </DOCNO> What we can learn from female chess prodigies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 42 </DOCNO> Selling plus-size clothing isn’t only about pleasing shoppers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 43 </DOCNO> Has the meaning of work changed forever? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 44 </DOCNO> Best of Worklife 2020 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 45 </DOCNO> Why the 'paradox mindset' is the key to success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 46 </DOCNO> Ellen Pao on how to make tech more diverse - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 47 </DOCNO> How outdoor advertising can deepen inequality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 48 </DOCNO> Why 'outskilling' isn’t yet a workplace revolution - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 49 </DOCNO> How major life events impact our long-term wellbeing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 50 </DOCNO> How young workers are changing the rules of 'business speak' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 51 </DOCNO> Equality Matters - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 52 </DOCNO> What happens to workplace perks when no-one’s in the office? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 53 </DOCNO> Bright Sparks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 54 </DOCNO> What animals tell us about female leadership - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 55 </DOCNO> Covid-19 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 56 </DOCNO> How Sweden is fixing the housework gender gap - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 57 </DOCNO> The corporate ideals driving ‘secret parenting’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 58 </DOCNO> The changes that could help women stay employed - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 59 </DOCNO> The strategy that turns daydreams into reality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 60 </DOCNO> The city that became an open-air café - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 61 </DOCNO> Canada’s forgotten universal basic income experiment - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 62 </DOCNO> Employment - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 63 </DOCNO> Why the cost of equality is a lot lower than we thought - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 64 </DOCNO> Remote Control - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 65 </DOCNO> Why the future of work might be ‘hybrid’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 66 </DOCNO> What makes strangers click? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 67 </DOCNO> Environment - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 68 </DOCNO> 'Heat gap': Why some city districts are hotter than others - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 69 </DOCNO> Best of Worklife 2019 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 70 </DOCNO> Why your ‘weak-tie’ friendships may mean more than you think - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 71 </DOCNO> Why this recession disproportionately affects women - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 72 </DOCNO> How to avoid burnout amid a pandemic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 73 </DOCNO> How Covid-19 has changed grocery shopping - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 74 </DOCNO> The 'paradox' of working in the world's most equal countries - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 75 </DOCNO> The most influential US workplace discrimination lawsuits - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 76 </DOCNO> How 'linguistic mirroring' can make you more convincing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 77 </DOCNO> How to make people like you – virtually - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 78 </DOCNO> Language - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 79 </DOCNO> What leader are you? It depends on your parents - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 80 </DOCNO> Language - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 81 </DOCNO> What Iceland can teach the world about gender pay gaps - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 82 </DOCNO> The Life Project - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 83 </DOCNO> Cyberloafing: The line between rejuvenating and wasting time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 84 </DOCNO> The trick that makes you overspend - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 85 </DOCNO> The tiny breaks that ease your body and reboot your brain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 86 </DOCNO> Holidays - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 87 </DOCNO> The office where everyone has a second job - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 88 </DOCNO> What the average American CEO looks like - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 89 </DOCNO> Why we should learn to love awful corporate buzzwords - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 90 </DOCNO> Owning Your Time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 91 </DOCNO> The ‘Batman Effect’: How having an alter ego empowers you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 92 </DOCNO> Should you start a company with your friend? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 93 </DOCNO> The rise of Japan's 'super solo' culture - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 94 </DOCNO> Why are we learning languages in a closed world? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 95 </DOCNO> The reasons why people become incompetent at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 96 </DOCNO> Perspectives - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 97 </DOCNO> What dress codes really mean for cabin crew - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 98 </DOCNO> What’s the best plan for a radical new workday? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 99 </DOCNO> How a 'growth mindset' can lead to success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 100 </DOCNO> This film lets you experience racism first-hand - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 101 </DOCNO> Will Coronavirus end India’s tapri chai culture? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 102 </DOCNO> Leadership - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 103 </DOCNO> The benefits isolation can have on your work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 104 </DOCNO> How anxiety affects your focus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 105 </DOCNO> The Life Project - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 106 </DOCNO> Why ‘healthy neurotics’ can thrive in stressful times - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 107 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How the world has had an 'unexpected chance to reset' our lives </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 108 </DOCNO> The evolution of home fitness - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 109 </DOCNO> Can you actually speak the languages you list on your CV? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 110 </DOCNO> The Diversity Box - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 111 </DOCNO> How to cut phone time at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 112 </DOCNO> The first step in transgender equality in the workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 113 </DOCNO> Collective Intelligence - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 114 </DOCNO> How the pandemic could redefine our productivity obsession - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 115 </DOCNO> Why virtual team-building activities feel agonising - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 116 </DOCNO> How self-control can actually unleash your dark side - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 117 </DOCNO> 'Samfundssind': How a long-forgotten word rallied a nation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 118 </DOCNO> How to politely and productively disagree - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 119 </DOCNO> How India's competitive exam-prep treadmill ground to a halt - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 120 </DOCNO> Where 75% of workers are on the autistic spectrum - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 121 </DOCNO> Will business travel ever be the same? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 122 </DOCNO> The Australian company that banned work on Wednesdays - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 123 </DOCNO> How can employees also be social-media activists? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 124 </DOCNO> Women shouldering ‘cost and burden’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 125 </DOCNO> Education - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 126 </DOCNO> Business Trip - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 127 </DOCNO> American parenting styles sweep Europe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 128 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How the world of work may change forever - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 129 </DOCNO> Why procrastination is about managing emotions, not time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 130 </DOCNO> Why open offices are bad for us - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 131 </DOCNO> Why happiness at work could be big business in India - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 132 </DOCNO> How to restore your sense of control when you feel powerless - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 133 </DOCNO> Could a ‘workcation’ change how you think? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 134 </DOCNO> Beating Burnout - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 135 </DOCNO> How offices will change after coronavirus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 136 </DOCNO> Could young workers change the future of labour? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 137 </DOCNO> Money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 138 </DOCNO> Spending - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 139 </DOCNO> Psychology of Work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 140 </DOCNO> A free-money programme that ‘turns lives around’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 141 </DOCNO> Why are some people better at working from home than others? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 142 </DOCNO> The simple maths error that can lead to bankruptcy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 143 </DOCNO> The algorithm tackling the office space crunch - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 144 </DOCNO> The four keys that could unlock procrastination - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 145 </DOCNO> The curious origins of online shopping - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 146 </DOCNO> How to function in times of uncertainty - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 147 </DOCNO> What to do with friends who don’t social distance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 148 </DOCNO> Should working while you commute count as paid time? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 149 </DOCNO> Four-day week - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 150 </DOCNO> The loopholes that disguise the gender pay gap - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 151 </DOCNO> Why self-compassion – not self-esteem – leads to success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 152 </DOCNO> Winnie Byanyima: Why quality jobs are so important - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 153 </DOCNO> Burnout is rising in the land of work-life balance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 154 </DOCNO> Why so many young Swedes live alone - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 155 </DOCNO> Productivity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 156 </DOCNO> How the ‘Ikea effect’ subtly influences how you spend - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 157 </DOCNO> Why making plans helps manage pandemic stress - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 158 </DOCNO> Does burnout recovery always require radical change? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 159 </DOCNO> The helpful upside of office personality tests - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 160 </DOCNO> Are you a 'cultural fit' for your job? Machines can now tell - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 161 </DOCNO> Why ‘worthless’ humanities degrees may set you up for life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 162 </DOCNO> The youngest tech pioneer in Ethiopia - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 163 </DOCNO> Why do we still distrust women leaders? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 164 </DOCNO> China's '996' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 165 </DOCNO> Why do we spend so much money on others? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 166 </DOCNO> The South Koreans left behind in a contact-free society - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 167 </DOCNO> How to tell if you’re close to burning out - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 168 </DOCNO> Can dogs help us avoid hiring bias? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 169 </DOCNO> How Hollywood earnings can help us understand pay disparity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 170 </DOCNO> Cognitive Load Theory: Explaining our fight for focus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 171 </DOCNO> White Day: Japan’s reverse Valentine’s Day - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 172 </DOCNO> Can Germans’ right to switch off survive the digital age? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 173 </DOCNO> The tiny home that can be built in four hours - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 174 </DOCNO> The holiday islands where locals have nowhere to live - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 175 </DOCNO> Nine surprising things worth more than this shimmering metal - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 176 </DOCNO> What wartime ‘munitionettes’ can teach us about burnout - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 177 </DOCNO> What it takes to be young, Greek and able to pay your bills - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 178 </DOCNO> The psychology behind 'revenge bedtime procrastination' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 179 </DOCNO> The fatalistic phrase that every culture has - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 180 </DOCNO> The mindset you need to succeed at every goal - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 181 </DOCNO> The biggest unknowns in a post-pandemic work world - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 182 </DOCNO> Unknown Questions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 183 </DOCNO> The curious origins of the dollar symbol - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 184 </DOCNO> The bias that makes us spend and not save - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 185 </DOCNO> The city where innovation is driven by necessity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 186 </DOCNO> Covid-19: The ways viruses can spread in offices - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 187 </DOCNO> How Japan is handling more ageing drivers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 188 </DOCNO> The personalities that benefit most from remote work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 189 </DOCNO> What LGBTI expats need from their employers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 190 </DOCNO> The rise of the pandemic-era 'gap year' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 191 </DOCNO> The Starbucks that's run completely by senior citizens - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 192 </DOCNO> The rush for Justin Timberlake’s shoes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 193 </DOCNO> Is now the time to tame Magaluf? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 194 </DOCNO> The rise of the sober bar - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 195 </DOCNO> This 12-year-old has made over $200K selling T-shirts - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 196 </DOCNO> The surprising perks of isolated work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 197 </DOCNO> Why arrogance is dangerously contagious - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 198 </DOCNO> Why we've been saying 'sorry' all wrong - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 199 </DOCNO> Why slowing your breathing helps you relax - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 200 </DOCNO> What's driving the rise of the McVegan burger? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 201 </DOCNO> Why this 18-year-old loves being a chimney sweep - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 202 </DOCNO> Fighting office sexism in Latin America - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 203 </DOCNO> Why Australia is doubling fees for arts degrees - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 204 </DOCNO> How Covid-19 could change plane boarding - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 205 </DOCNO> Skiplagging: The travel trick that airlines hate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 206 </DOCNO> This man wants to get rid of the office for good - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 207 </DOCNO> The online ‘work gyms’ that help spur productivity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 208 </DOCNO> The virtual vloggers taking over YouTube - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 209 </DOCNO> Hong Kong’s public space problem - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 210 </DOCNO> The evolution of the modern workday - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 211 </DOCNO> Would you pay $25 for a nap? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 212 </DOCNO> How can a distracted generation learn anything? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 213 </DOCNO> Could adding a new public holiday boost the economy? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 214 </DOCNO> Health - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 215 </DOCNO> How to tell if you’re being ‘breadcrumbed’ at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 216 </DOCNO> The secrets of the ‘high-potential’ personality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 217 </DOCNO> Worklife 101 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 218 </DOCNO> What 10 famous people say about the humanities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 219 </DOCNO> Could bartering become the new buying in a changed world? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 220 </DOCNO> How to work on a huge news day - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 221 </DOCNO> Generation Project - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 222 </DOCNO> What do we look for in a ‘good’ robot colleague? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 223 </DOCNO> Pretending you care can help your career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 224 </DOCNO> The rise of ‘happiness coaches’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 225 </DOCNO> How one teen’s app stops cyberbullying before it starts - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 226 </DOCNO> Why plastic-surgery demand is booming amid lockdown - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 227 </DOCNO> Student - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 228 </DOCNO> Why airlines make flights longer on purpose - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 229 </DOCNO> The changing buzzwords of business books - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 230 </DOCNO> Meet the geek behind Egypt’s hit online science show - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 231 </DOCNO> Does music help us work better? It depends - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 232 </DOCNO> Cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 233 </DOCNO> How the pay gap starts while we are still teenagers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 234 </DOCNO> Why litter is surging as lockdowns ease - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 235 </DOCNO> Work-life balance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 236 </DOCNO> The rise of employee health tracking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 237 </DOCNO> Yes,  you should tell everyone about your failures - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 238 </DOCNO> The best city for working families? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 239 </DOCNO> The 27-year-old inventor helping kids speak through toys - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 240 </DOCNO> What 50 years of remote work teaches us - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 241 </DOCNO> Best of 2018 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 242 </DOCNO> Why so many people overspend on their holidays - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 243 </DOCNO> Asynchronous video interviews: The tools you need to succeed - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 244 </DOCNO> Why sexual harassment training doesn’t work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 245 </DOCNO> Why an off-the-grid hour at work is so crucial - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 246 </DOCNO> Personal Finance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 247 </DOCNO> There is one quality that builds trust and loyalty - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 248 </DOCNO> The Greek plan to bring tourists back - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 249 </DOCNO> The coronavirus effect on Pakistan’s digital divide - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 250 </DOCNO> The new tech that detects deadly slides on rubbish mountains - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 251 </DOCNO> Jantelagen: Why Swedes won’t talk about wealth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 252 </DOCNO> Sisu: The Finnish art of inner strength - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 253 </DOCNO> How to plan your day to get the best out of your brain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 254 </DOCNO> The new residency schemes inviting workers abroad - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 255 </DOCNO> How to spot a lying job candidate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 256 </DOCNO> How to stamp out sexual harassment in the workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 257 </DOCNO> The benefits of note-taking by hand - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 258 </DOCNO> The unrealistic expectations of retirement behaviour - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 259 </DOCNO> The barber who's been cutting hair for 96 years - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 260 </DOCNO> Stress - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 261 </DOCNO> The haughty history of the letter H - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 262 </DOCNO> How students turn to 'essay mills' to help them cheat - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 263 </DOCNO> The 27-year-old protecting Brazil's hidden job economy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 264 </DOCNO> Why suffering setbacks could make you more successful - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 265 </DOCNO> The strategies that get you through tough challenges - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 266 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How can society thrive post-pandemic? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 267 </DOCNO> Yes, you should really 'be yourself' at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 268 </DOCNO> Life after lockdown: How China went back to work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 269 </DOCNO> When productivity becomes an addiction - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 270 </DOCNO> Why your wages aren’t going up - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 271 </DOCNO> How much free time do we really have? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 272 </DOCNO> Smart Travel - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 273 </DOCNO> The young woman who wants to put bees in your office - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 274 </DOCNO> Power of an Hour - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 275 </DOCNO> Why some people are impossibly talented - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 276 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: The psychology of panic buying - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 277 </DOCNO> How to learn a language in an hour a day - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 278 </DOCNO> Does a cashless society benefit everyone? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 279 </DOCNO> Young Chinese are sick of working long hours - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 280 </DOCNO> Unemployment during coronavirus: The psychology of job loss - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 281 </DOCNO> These are the worst things about working in an open office - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 282 </DOCNO> Inside the homes of maximalists and minimalists - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 283 </DOCNO> What the future of conferences could look like - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 284 </DOCNO> Expats - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 285 </DOCNO> Inside Brazil’s hidden daycare economy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 286 </DOCNO> How lockdowns are changing our friendship groups - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 287 </DOCNO> Communication - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 288 </DOCNO> Will the High Streets get shoppers back? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 289 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How much news is too much? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 290 </DOCNO> The fight against compulsive shopping that takes a year - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 291 </DOCNO> Confined Grind - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 292 </DOCNO> How to become an ‘elastic thinker’ and problem solver - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 293 </DOCNO> Worklife 101 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 294 </DOCNO> Success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 295 </DOCNO> Why email loses out to popular apps in China - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 296 </DOCNO> Ageing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 297 </DOCNO> The senior nomads who sold everything to travel the world - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 298 </DOCNO> Gen J - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 299 </DOCNO> The most successful companies are also the luckiest - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 300 </DOCNO> Why we look to nature in uncertain times - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 301 </DOCNO> How to avoid writing irritating emails - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 302 </DOCNO> How to take a digital detox during the Covid-19 pandemic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 303 </DOCNO> What the Dutch can teach the world about remote work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 304 </DOCNO> Your hand gestures can help make you more charismatic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 305 </DOCNO> Vegan seafood: The next plant-based meat trend? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 306 </DOCNO> How Covid-19 led to a nationwide work-from-home experiment - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 307 </DOCNO> China’s influencer incubator - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 308 </DOCNO> How ‘dark patterns’ influence travel bookings - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 309 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How to avoid overeating when working from home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 310 </DOCNO> The Norwegian art of the packed lunch - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 311 </DOCNO> How 'Feierabend' helps Germans disconnect from the workday - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 312 </DOCNO> Why the Swiss still love cash - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 313 </DOCNO> ‘Our formula for happiness and success is backwards’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 314 </DOCNO> The strategy that turns daydreams into reality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 315 </DOCNO> Five trends that will change how we work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 316 </DOCNO> Why your New Year’s resolutions often fail - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 317 </DOCNO> Burnout - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 318 </DOCNO> The problem with perfectionists - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 319 </DOCNO> Why do we feel uneasy about a ‘new normal’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 320 </DOCNO> Top working from home tips from around the world - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 321 </DOCNO> How to be a better tourist - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 322 </DOCNO> How ‘emergency reserves’ can help you stick to your goals - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 323 </DOCNO> Workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 324 </DOCNO> Is there a best time of year to buy stocks? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 325 </DOCNO> A guide for the 'all about me' generation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 326 </DOCNO> How to master new skills with ‘deliberate practice’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 327 </DOCNO> How many days should you take off work? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 328 </DOCNO> The compelling case for working a lot less - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 329 </DOCNO> Is gap-year volunteering a luxury for the rich? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 330 </DOCNO> Should you get paid based on where you live? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 331 </DOCNO> The best mental health tips for staying sane in isolation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 332 </DOCNO> Why Germans are flying less - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 333 </DOCNO> Does more money make you work harder? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 334 </DOCNO> Meetings are terrible. Can an elite team fix that? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 335 </DOCNO> The neglected benefits of the commute - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 336 </DOCNO> The gender pay gap no-one talks about - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 337 </DOCNO> The smart guide to procrastination - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 338 </DOCNO> The myth of being 'bad' at maths - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 339 </DOCNO> How to work from home with your kids during coronavirus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 340 </DOCNO> Super apps - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 341 </DOCNO> The ‘law’ that explains why you can't get anything done - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 342 </DOCNO> Are we too broke to stick to our principles? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 343 </DOCNO> The young Koreans pushing back on a culture of endurance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 344 </DOCNO> Some firms give more time off to those who shun plane travel - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 345 </DOCNO> How to work from home – comfortably - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 346 </DOCNO> Dealing with clients who expect you to work for nothing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 347 </DOCNO> How to cultivate a daily reading habit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 348 </DOCNO> Bossy, bossy, bossy – should we ban it? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 349 </DOCNO> The workspace that takes away your phone - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 350 </DOCNO> Why so many of the world’s oldest companies are in Japan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 351 </DOCNO> Psychology - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 352 </DOCNO> How busyness leads to bad decisions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 353 </DOCNO> The great shrinking airline seat </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 354 </DOCNO> How thinking like a toddler could help you get ahead - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 355 </DOCNO>  </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 356 </DOCNO> The 106-year history of the dreaded economy airline seat - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 357 </DOCNO> How Japan could reinvent the hotel - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 358 </DOCNO> The body-clock science behind later school start times - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 359 </DOCNO> Why walking makes you a better worker - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 360 </DOCNO> The Swiss court ruling on home workers’ rent - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 361 </DOCNO> Why appraisals are pointless for most people - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 362 </DOCNO> Will Covid-19 make urban cycling more inclusive? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 363 </DOCNO> You can win a billion and still go bankrupt - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 364 </DOCNO> How hidden bias can stop you getting a job - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 365 </DOCNO> The foreign workers leaving Britain because of Brexit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 366 </DOCNO> The legitimate concerns of ‘snowflake’ workers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 367 </DOCNO> The ‘condescending old people’ of South Korea's workforce - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 368 </DOCNO> The married couples in Hong Kong who live apart - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 369 </DOCNO> Why getting distracted can be a very good thing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 370 </DOCNO> What remote jobs tell us about inequality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 371 </DOCNO> How to escape the ‘hyperactive hivemind’ of modern work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 372 </DOCNO> The painstaking story behind the euro symbol - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 373 </DOCNO> How to conquer work paralysis like Ernest Hemingway - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 374 </DOCNO> Seoul power: Asia’s unlikely expat haven - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 375 </DOCNO> How Japan's #KuToo fights pressure to wear high heels - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 376 </DOCNO> A service for ‘renting minorities’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 377 </DOCNO> How 'reading the air' keeps Japan running - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 378 </DOCNO> This is why you can’t switch off at the weekend - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 379 </DOCNO> Economics - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 380 </DOCNO> The future of Japan's master artisans - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 381 </DOCNO> The Korean CSAT is the exam that stops a nation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 382 </DOCNO> Coronavirus isolation is creating new couples - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 383 </DOCNO> Will coronavirus change Germans’ love of cash? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 384 </DOCNO> More seniors, more foreigners: How Japan is changing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 385 </DOCNO> The cities that supercharge your career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 386 </DOCNO> The things that do – and don't – motivate kids to succeed - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 387 </DOCNO> The strange reason owl theft may be on the rise - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 388 </DOCNO> Does an extra hour of sleep matter? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 389 </DOCNO> What the world can learn from Japan’s robots - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 390 </DOCNO>  </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 391 </DOCNO> Should you start your day at 2:30 in the morning? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 392 </DOCNO> There is an elite society to fulfil the wishes of the rich - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 393 </DOCNO> How Slovenia uses the sound of bees to relax - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 394 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: How to work from home, the right way - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 395 </DOCNO> Neurodiversity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 396 </DOCNO> How ‘biophilic’ design can create a better workspace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 397 </DOCNO> ‘It’s actually really good to get rejected’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 398 </DOCNO> The innovators offering expats cheaper schools - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 399 </DOCNO> It takes a CEO just days to earn your annual wage - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 400 </DOCNO> Viewpoints - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 401 </DOCNO> How to stop ‘digital gangsters’ stealing your time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 402 </DOCNO> What makes a recipe go viral? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 403 </DOCNO> Is there an answer to millennial burnout? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 404 </DOCNO> Europe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 405 </DOCNO> How a nation of introverts meets up - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 406 </DOCNO> Social media - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 407 </DOCNO> The learning opportunities hiding in our failures - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 408 </DOCNO> Expat Guide - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 409 </DOCNO> Why grocery shelves won't be empty for long - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 410 </DOCNO> A novel way to prevent email overload - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 411 </DOCNO> Is click-and-collect the future of shopping? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 412 </DOCNO> How to exercise during the workday (and why it's important) - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 413 </DOCNO> Is Singapore really the world’s most expensive city? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 414 </DOCNO> How a corporate mission can drive young workers away - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 415 </DOCNO> Presenteeism - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 416 </DOCNO> The subtle power of uncomfortable silences - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 417 </DOCNO> Business - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 418 </DOCNO> The companies that help people vanish - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 419 </DOCNO> How to make deadlines motivating, not stressful - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 420 </DOCNO> What the German language reveals about attitudes to work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 421 </DOCNO> How Covid-19 will change our shopping habits - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 422 </DOCNO> China - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 423 </DOCNO> Working between liberal Lisbon and conservative Dubai - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 424 </DOCNO> Focus on how you work, not why - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 425 </DOCNO> Can young people thrive in a remote-work world? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 427 </DOCNO> Is stress good or bad? It’s actually both - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 426 </DOCNO> Technology - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 428 </DOCNO> Managing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 429 </DOCNO> How to identify, and handle, a demanding boss - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 430 </DOCNO> Constantly late with work? Blame the planning fallacy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 431 </DOCNO> Can festive cheer boost your language skills? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 432 </DOCNO> The 'romance scammers' cashing in on lockdown loneliness - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 433 </DOCNO> Is this phrase the Swiss Army knife of Japanese? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 434 </DOCNO> The Future of Shopping - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 435 </DOCNO> Does your boss consider you a 'non-talent'? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 436 </DOCNO> France’s battle against an ‘always-on’ work culture - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 437 </DOCNO> Do office reopenings mean a return to the 'old normal'? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 438 </DOCNO> New Zealand’s ‘brain gain’ boost - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 439 </DOCNO> Will coronavirus change how we define heroes? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 440 </DOCNO> Business Traveller - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 441 </DOCNO> Sitzfleisch: The German concept to get more work done - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 442 </DOCNO> Is the UAE still a high-paid expat haven? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 443 </DOCNO> You could have a workplace rival and not even know it - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 444 </DOCNO> Why time management so often fails - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 445 </DOCNO> Email - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 446 </DOCNO> The daily dances of Beijing's rival restaurants - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 447 </DOCNO> Why you should keep a connection with your expat country - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 448 </DOCNO> Will Covid-19 end the handshake? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 449 </DOCNO> How Vienna became a commerce hotspot - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 450 </DOCNO> The art of perseverance: How gaman defined Japan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 451 </DOCNO> How people are 'ghosting' their employers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 452 </DOCNO> The ‘stress interview’: a technique that goes too far? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 453 </DOCNO> Rise and grind - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 454 </DOCNO> How ‘survivorship bias’ can cause you to make mistakes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 455 </DOCNO> How our views on work have changed forever - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 456 </DOCNO> When the boss is a psychopath - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 457 </DOCNO> No retirement home for me, thanks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 458 </DOCNO> The extravagant brunches of expat elites - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 459 </DOCNO> How to say no at work when you don't have kids - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 460 </DOCNO> Can you train people to be less prejudiced? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 461 </DOCNO> How workplaces are phasing out the tattoo stigma - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 462 </DOCNO> Pet acupuncture finds popularity in China - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 463 </DOCNO> Japan 2020 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 464 </DOCNO> Why saying ‘no’ will boost your career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 465 </DOCNO> Why Finland leads the world in flexible work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 466 </DOCNO> Time Hackers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 467 </DOCNO> Where you sign a $10m contract over a pint - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 468 </DOCNO> The top seven places to retire - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 469 </DOCNO> The remote work experiment that upped productivity 13% - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 470 </DOCNO> Those ‘most expensive city’ lists are designed for expats - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 471 </DOCNO> Housing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 472 </DOCNO> China’s cliff-climbing ‘spiderwoman’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 473 </DOCNO> Wellness - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 474 </DOCNO> Why office noise bothers some people more than others - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 475 </DOCNO> What if you never saw your colleagues in person again? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 476 </DOCNO> Why it's not always good to be consistent - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 477 </DOCNO> The woman who lives in six cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 478 </DOCNO> Saving - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 479 </DOCNO> Careers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 480 </DOCNO> Unconscious bias - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 481 </DOCNO> Networking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 482 </DOCNO> What's really holding women back in the workplace? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 483 </DOCNO> Can a fear of getting fired make you work harder? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 484 </DOCNO> The Swedish staycation obsession - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 485 </DOCNO> China’s ‘Pearl Bro’ making millions from live streaming - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 486 </DOCNO> The sweet-maker teaching Google about creativity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 487 </DOCNO> How women's workwear has evolved - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 488 </DOCNO> Longevity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 489 </DOCNO> What hermits can teach us about isolation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 490 </DOCNO> Luxury - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 491 </DOCNO> The high cost of avoiding the draft - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 492 </DOCNO> Why the US is drawing in Europe’s expats post-Brexit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 493 </DOCNO> The solution for open office frustration - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 494 </DOCNO> The Nordic Way - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 495 </DOCNO> How the busiest people plan their days - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 496 </DOCNO> We need to talk about dyslexia at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 497 </DOCNO> Resilience: A Lesson From Sochi - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 498 </DOCNO> You probably suffer from scattered brain syndrome - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 499 </DOCNO> The weird world of the Western workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 500 </DOCNO> Will empty middle seats help social distancing on planes? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 501 </DOCNO> Can you get a $21K pay rise by moving abroad? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 502 </DOCNO> An expat’s dream post, but opportunities are drying up - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 503 </DOCNO> Can the ‘Centenarian Olympics’ help you live longer? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 504 </DOCNO> The bias that can cause catastrophe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 505 </DOCNO> The saboteurs you can hire to end your relationship - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 506 </DOCNO> When opening that new office is really all about your ego - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 507 </DOCNO> The enduring magic of the voice actor - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 508 </DOCNO> Procrastination nannies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 509 </DOCNO> Future Thinking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 510 </DOCNO> The modern phenomenon of the weekend - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 511 </DOCNO> Level Up - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 512 </DOCNO> What nobody tells you about becoming the boss - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 513 </DOCNO> Language Matters  - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 514 </DOCNO> The YouTube stars who teach the world about Japan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 515 </DOCNO> Is video dating here to stay? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 516 </DOCNO> Six tips for better work-life balance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 517 </DOCNO> The surprise ingredient one chef never leaves behind - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 518 </DOCNO> Is this the secret to living longer? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 519 </DOCNO> Is this the best time in history to learn languages? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 520 </DOCNO> Toxic boss? Here's what to do - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 521 </DOCNO> The subtle reasons why leaders ignore their own advice - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 522 </DOCNO> Biometric CVs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 523 </DOCNO> Why you don’t want a nice boss - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 524 </DOCNO> How firms move to secret offices amid Covid-19 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 525 </DOCNO> Millennial bosses - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 526 </DOCNO> Are people misinterpreting your email sign-off? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 527 </DOCNO> Gardening could be the hobby that helps you live to 100 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 528 </DOCNO> Bad bosses — or bad hiring? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 529 </DOCNO> All eyes on Malmo, but not because of Trump - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 530 </DOCNO> How video games turn teenagers into millionaires - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 531 </DOCNO> Can classes help Seoul’s marriage-phobic singles? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 532 </DOCNO> How Hong Kong is modernising love hotels - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 533 </DOCNO> How factories change production to quickly fight coronavirus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 534 </DOCNO> The best places to retire for the adventurous - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 535 </DOCNO> Why you shouldn’t try to be a morning person - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 536 </DOCNO> The 101 people, ideas and things changing how we work today - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 537 </DOCNO> What keeps workers going when it’s not all about the money? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 538 </DOCNO> Are we born leaders? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 539 </DOCNO> How an ancient tradition shaped a nation's work ethic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 540 </DOCNO> Japan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 541 </DOCNO> There’s more to this chic French town than movie stars - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 542 </DOCNO> How the wellness industry is taking over travel - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 543 </DOCNO> Why we’ve created new language for coronavirus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 544 </DOCNO> Corporate nomads - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 545 </DOCNO> Taming the toxic office grumbler - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 546 </DOCNO> Entrepreneur - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 547 </DOCNO> There’s no such thing as flexible work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 548 </DOCNO> The jobs in India that attract thousands of applicants - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 549 </DOCNO> The baby boomers taking a 'golden' gap year - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 550 </DOCNO> Modern language - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 551 </DOCNO> Life hacks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 552 </DOCNO> How gender inequality lasts into death - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 553 </DOCNO> Why millennials are heading for a wilder tech city - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 554 </DOCNO> How online gaming has become a social lifeline - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 555 </DOCNO> Juggling kids, business and a cross-continental commute - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 556 </DOCNO> Car-free cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 557 </DOCNO> This is why the boss will crush all your good ideas - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 558 </DOCNO> An illustrated guide to making better decisions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 559 </DOCNO> Flygskam - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 560 </DOCNO> Having a baby in your 40s or later? Consider this - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 561 </DOCNO> Inside the life of a yacht broker to the rich and famous - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 562 </DOCNO> How to tame your nightmare boss - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 563 </DOCNO> Which country works the longest hours? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 564 </DOCNO> Why your in-office friendships still matter - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 565 </DOCNO> Why indoor air quality matters to our bodies and our brains - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 566 </DOCNO> Can £27m a year bring a language back from near death? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 567 </DOCNO> The one thing ruining your free time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 568 </DOCNO> With Brexit on the horizon, Frankfurt's star is on the rise - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 569 </DOCNO> The keys to inspired leadership - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 570 </DOCNO> Why the world now has more grandparents than grandchildren - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 571 </DOCNO> Japan's #KuToo - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 572 </DOCNO> The 10 biggest misconceptions about being a leader - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 573 </DOCNO> A silent struggle in the workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 574 </DOCNO> Why is this British company selling ice to Swedes? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 575 </DOCNO> The Japanese city that banned ‘smartphone-walking’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 576 </DOCNO> Why 'unlimited' time off isn't actually unlimited - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 577 </DOCNO> Wealth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 578 </DOCNO> What is the future of English in the US? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 579 </DOCNO> The surprising traits of good remote leaders - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 580 </DOCNO> Spain’s fight against unpaid overtime - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 581 </DOCNO> Friluftsliv: The Nordic concept of getting outdoors - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 582 </DOCNO> The strange psychology of stress and burnout - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 583 </DOCNO> Why do workplace dress codes persist? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 584 </DOCNO> Why you don’t give praise in Japan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 585 </DOCNO> Davos - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 586 </DOCNO> Ghost work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 587 </DOCNO> Yes, it’s possible to retire in your 30s - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 588 </DOCNO> Does this city have the best food and wine in France? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 589 </DOCNO> Are Europe's night trains back in fashion? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 590 </DOCNO> A South Korean ‘prison’ for people seeking peace and quiet - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 591 </DOCNO> Stephen Hawking's advice for a fulfilling career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 592 </DOCNO> Family Values - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 593 </DOCNO> Why working from home might be less sustainable - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 594 </DOCNO> Is this Asia’s best stopover city? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 595 </DOCNO> Forget what Trump says, why Brussels is no #hellhole - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 596 </DOCNO> Microgrids - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 597 </DOCNO> Will you work to 100? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 598 </DOCNO> Why being offline is overrated - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 599 </DOCNO> Eight ways virtual personal assistants could work for you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 600 </DOCNO> How did the vegan sausage roll get so popular? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 601 </DOCNO> A city emerging from a junta’s grip - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 602 </DOCNO> How shorter workweeks could save Earth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 603 </DOCNO> The tequila boss who travels 120,000 miles a year - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 604 </DOCNO> Why do some companies ban certain words? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 605 </DOCNO> The man who hacks his own body - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 606 </DOCNO> How being realistic can be key to your wellbeing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 607 </DOCNO> Transport - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 608 </DOCNO> The woman who travels 135,000 miles a year for work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 609 </DOCNO> Where Christmas trees cost a month's pay - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 610 </DOCNO> Here's why you could explore this city 'for a lifetime' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 611 </DOCNO> Sustainability - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 612 </DOCNO> Is full-time work bad for our brains? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 613 </DOCNO> Think before you overshare. Yes, it can get you fired - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 614 </DOCNO> Virtual talent agencies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 615 </DOCNO> The call no one wants to receive - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 616 </DOCNO> The reason employers love online job portals - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 617 </DOCNO> Mansplaining, explained in one simple chart - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 618 </DOCNO> ‘You can come from nowhere and become somebody here’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 619 </DOCNO> Unknown Questions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 620 </DOCNO> The man who delivers to monks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 621 </DOCNO> Boring office wellness alternatives that actually work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 622 </DOCNO> ‘Gluten-free water’ and other absurd labelling trends - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 623 </DOCNO> This once-dark city is becoming the darling of Europe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 624 </DOCNO> The commas that cost companies millions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 625 </DOCNO> Do psychopaths really make better leaders? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 626 </DOCNO> Meet Australia’s new go-it-alone investors - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 627 </DOCNO> Unlimited holidays - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 628 </DOCNO> The many upsides of a happy workforce - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 629 </DOCNO> Experts critiqued da Vinci's CV. They weren't impressed - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 630 </DOCNO> What most bosses get wrong about millennials - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 631 </DOCNO> The science of creating a dream team - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 632 </DOCNO> Why there are so many Japanese emoji - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 633 </DOCNO> Smile, you’re in Asia’s friendliest metropolis - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 634 </DOCNO> Workplace bullying is more harmful than we realised - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 635 </DOCNO> Why do ill people still come in to work? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 636 </DOCNO> Women and Work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 637 </DOCNO> The true importance of good spelling - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 638 </DOCNO> This is what the Davos social media machine looks like - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 639 </DOCNO> The ripple effects of closed office buildings - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 640 </DOCNO> How recruiters are stalking you on Facebook - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 641 </DOCNO> How multitasking sabotages you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 642 </DOCNO> Baby Boomers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 643 </DOCNO> How AI can help us harness our 'collective intelligence' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 644 </DOCNO> TikTok - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 645 </DOCNO> Is this the best time to be productive? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 646 </DOCNO> Is Sweden the best place to lose your job? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 647 </DOCNO> Are you an ‘insecure overachiever’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 648 </DOCNO> What is the Worklife 101? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 649 </DOCNO> How one city transformed from grey to glitzy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 650 </DOCNO> How to avoid the ‘competency trap’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 651 </DOCNO> Managing global millennials: put your stereotypes aside - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 652 </DOCNO> The food you buy really is shrinking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 653 </DOCNO> Small Business - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 654 </DOCNO> Can’t unplug? Here’s how to navigate your digital anxiety - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 655 </DOCNO> The entrepreneurs making money out of thin air - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 656 </DOCNO> How elite teams increase their emotional intelligence - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 657 </DOCNO> Real delegation requires something unexpected - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 658 </DOCNO> Blowing the whistle on the pay gap - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 659 </DOCNO> Why this is Europe’s best work-and-play capital - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 660 </DOCNO> Diversity tracking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 661 </DOCNO> What to do when your great promotion backfires - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 662 </DOCNO> Is ‘dopamine fasting’ Silicon Valley’s new productivity fad? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 663 </DOCNO> How your workplace is killing you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 664 </DOCNO> The ‘imported’ priests saving Ireland’s ageing clergy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 665 </DOCNO> ‘Have a beer, smile, and don’t be afraid to chat’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 666 </DOCNO> Forget the boys’ club, welcome to the girls’ club - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 667 </DOCNO> Is this the secret of smart leadership? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 668 </DOCNO> How to get ahead in the era of the show-off - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 669 </DOCNO> The myth of executive accountability - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 670 </DOCNO> Meet the true kings and queens of Facebook and Snapchat - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 671 </DOCNO> Algorithms are making us small-minded - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 672 </DOCNO> These coffee snobs ban milk and sugar - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 673 </DOCNO> This teenager made $7,000 last year as a drone photographer - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 674 </DOCNO> Can artificial intelligence fight elderly loneliness? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 675 </DOCNO> One of the world's brainiest cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 676 </DOCNO> Will coronavirus make flying more expensive? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 677 </DOCNO> The Danish trick to “shock” your body into happiness - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 678 </DOCNO> What will Japan do with all of its empty ‘ghost’ homes? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 679 </DOCNO> Why young Londoners are moving to houseboats - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 680 </DOCNO> Would you share your job with someone? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 681 </DOCNO> How can bosses put a stop to workers idly browsing online? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 682 </DOCNO> How can a fast food chain ever make money from a $1 burger? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 683 </DOCNO> Is this South America’s unexpected boomtown? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 684 </DOCNO> The woman matching pooches and people - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 685 </DOCNO> How coronavirus has transformed the way we communicate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 686 </DOCNO> The country running out of space for its millionaires - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 687 </DOCNO> The colourful way South Korean workers cope with long hours - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 688 </DOCNO> Are community currencies a better way to shop? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 689 </DOCNO> Harsh realities of being a professional 'girl gamer' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 690 </DOCNO> Why the Canadian town of Asbestos wants a new name - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 691 </DOCNO> Why Japan celebrates Christmas with KFC - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 692 </DOCNO> Why you can’t afford to ignore nature in the workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 693 </DOCNO> What’s really driving the boom in wellness foods? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 694 </DOCNO> The couples rethinking kids because of climate change - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 695 </DOCNO> What drives an elite ‘super tutor’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 696 </DOCNO> Food - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 697 </DOCNO> Living without electricity in the heart of Seoul - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 698 </DOCNO> The man behind the million-dollar homepage - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 699 </DOCNO> The new, subtle ways the rich signal their wealth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 700 </DOCNO> JOMO - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 701 </DOCNO> Why are people thirsty for 'raw water'? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 702 </DOCNO> Is this the world’s quirkiest capital? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 703 </DOCNO> Why young Germans think this career is the wurst - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 704 </DOCNO> The world's fastest growing cities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 705 </DOCNO> The former tech CEO obsessed with walking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 706 </DOCNO> Canada - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 707 </DOCNO> Networking for people who hate to network - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 708 </DOCNO> Michael Phelps: 'It’s OK to not be OK' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 709 </DOCNO> You’ll need seven months’ rent for a flat in this city - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 710 </DOCNO> The science behind giving good gifts - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 711 </DOCNO> Is this the best city for after-work adventure? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 712 </DOCNO> Are rich people heartless? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 713 </DOCNO> The most expensive beauty products designed by science - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 714 </DOCNO> How to stop lying to yourself - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 715 </DOCNO> Video - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 716 </DOCNO> Can price hikes by businesses ever be justified? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 717 </DOCNO> Cycling v public transport: How do cities compare? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 718 </DOCNO> What Japan’s love of nostalgia says about its economy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 719 </DOCNO> Why claiming 'job turf' could help improve your pay - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 720 </DOCNO> What would happen if we all took smart drugs? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 721 </DOCNO> How burnout affects mental health workers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 722 </DOCNO> How customer complaints help companies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 723 </DOCNO> Does it make sense to pay people to have kids? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 724 </DOCNO> BBC - Worklife - The lifelong exercise that keeps Japan moving </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 725 </DOCNO> The German 'Quereinsteiger' ending career-changing stigma - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 726 </DOCNO> Inside the competitive world of luxury marriage proposals - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 727 </DOCNO> A fractured life, put back together </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 728 </DOCNO> The woman behind the morning dance party craze - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 729 </DOCNO> The people sent in to fix toxic office relationships - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 730 </DOCNO> Innovation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 731 </DOCNO> The hidden private experiences of the travel elite - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 732 </DOCNO> He lived in a prison to save for a house deposit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 733 </DOCNO> Opinion: Getting rich has more to do with luck than talent - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 734 </DOCNO> How the Japanese are putting an end to extreme work weeks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 735 </DOCNO> Augmented Realities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 736 </DOCNO> Right-to-repair movement - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 737 </DOCNO> The village with more wolves than children - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 738 </DOCNO> What Halloween will look like during Covid-19 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 739 </DOCNO> How perfectionism leads to depression - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 740 </DOCNO> Are millennials on track to become the richest generation? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 741 </DOCNO> This is why Christmas creep makes us cringe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 742 </DOCNO> Why we’re drinking more Champagne than ever before - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 743 </DOCNO> Why you sometimes have to quit to win - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 744 </DOCNO> Should you dump your smartphone for a flip-phone? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 745 </DOCNO> The hidden sexism in workplace language - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 746 </DOCNO> What everyone gets wrong about 'millennial snowflakes' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 747 </DOCNO> Hidden likes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 748 </DOCNO> Tips for longevity from the oldest people on Earth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 749 </DOCNO> Jantelagen: the code where mentioning wealth is taboo - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 750 </DOCNO> The rise of the ‘virtual water cooler’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 751 </DOCNO> Do Brits and Americans really understand each other? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 752 </DOCNO> Why micromanaging isn’t such a dirty word - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 753 </DOCNO> The arm’s-length flats of Tokyo - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 754 </DOCNO> This is where green policies make financial sense - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 755 </DOCNO> Why shopping is about to become all about the experience - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 756 </DOCNO> The countries where cash is on the verge of extinction - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 757 </DOCNO> A lust for speed: Young, rich and Chinese in rural America - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 758 </DOCNO> A global perspective on working mothers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 759 </DOCNO> For a slam dunk at work, know these sport terms - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 760 </DOCNO> The feminisation of alcohol marketing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 761 </DOCNO> The MeToo evolution - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 762 </DOCNO> Five tips to look your best on video calls - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 763 </DOCNO> The cities designing playgrounds for the elderly - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 764 </DOCNO> Why citizenship is now a commodity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 765 </DOCNO> China’s lucrative caffeine craze - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 766 </DOCNO> The secret language you speak without realising it - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 767 </DOCNO> The real cost of being a wedding guest - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 768 </DOCNO> The Conversation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 769 </DOCNO> Balancing work and life in the city that never sleeps - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 770 </DOCNO> How did our ancestors avoid distractions? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 771 </DOCNO> The town fighting its killer reputation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 772 </DOCNO> Shopping a sale gives you the same feeling as getting high - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 773 </DOCNO> Sky's the Limit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 774 </DOCNO> Is Kylie Jenner really a ‘self-made’ millionaire? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 775 </DOCNO> Native English speakers are the world’s worst communicators - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 776 </DOCNO> Credit card fraud: What you need to know - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 777 </DOCNO> Longevity economy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 778 </DOCNO> Is this the next Korean obsession? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 779 </DOCNO> Finland’s €10,000 babies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 780 </DOCNO> The uncertain present and future for recent graduates - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 781 </DOCNO> The Zoom social etiquette guide - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 782 </DOCNO> Productivity playlists - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 783 </DOCNO> The new trick to get you spending more - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 784 </DOCNO> Is cycling to work really cheaper than public transport? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 785 </DOCNO> How rich are you, really? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 786 </DOCNO> What's the real price of getting rid of plastic packaging? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 787 </DOCNO> You need to go back to school to relearn English - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 788 </DOCNO> Alternative Investing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 789 </DOCNO> Whatever happened to Berlin’s deserted ‘ghost’ airport? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 790 </DOCNO> South Korea’s population paradox - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 791 </DOCNO> Passion exploitation - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 792 </DOCNO> This parking space costs more than your house - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 793 </DOCNO> The auction catering to China’s elite collectors - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 794 </DOCNO> Is Airbnb making it impossible to find a house? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 795 </DOCNO> How to make the right decisions under pressure - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 796 </DOCNO> These are the toys that will make you smarter at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 797 </DOCNO> Even English speakers are baffled by these words - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 798 </DOCNO> Population Paradox - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 799 </DOCNO> How cities trick you into better behaviour - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 800 </DOCNO> The mental hacks that level up your self-control - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 801 </DOCNO> The people who pay $27,000 to work abroad - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 802 </DOCNO> The most coveted cigars will never be smoked. Here’s why - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 803 </DOCNO> Digital detox - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 804 </DOCNO> How to fail like a leader - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 805 </DOCNO> The UK’s most slippery export - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 806 </DOCNO> Meet the people who’ve retired at sea - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 807 </DOCNO> Should Spain replace the siesta with flexible work? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 808 </DOCNO> How to tell someone they suck – the British way - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 809 </DOCNO> The man who swims to work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 810 </DOCNO> The untapped potential of the ‘longevity economy’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 811 </DOCNO> The enduring dilemma of the working mother - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 812 </DOCNO> People analytics - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 813 </DOCNO> The psychology behind spending big - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 814 </DOCNO> Millennial - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 815 </DOCNO> Does your accent make you sound smarter? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 816 </DOCNO> This is how to give customers what they want - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 817 </DOCNO> The hidden psychology of failure - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 818 </DOCNO> Affording Your Life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 819 </DOCNO> Masayoshi Son - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 820 </DOCNO> The special skills power couples cultivate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 821 </DOCNO> Blame your worthless workdays on ‘meeting recovery syndrome’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 822 </DOCNO> The country where mothers win medals for having more kids - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 823 </DOCNO> Ikigai: A Japanese concept to improve work and life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 824 </DOCNO> Retirement - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 825 </DOCNO> How to pull yourself back from the brink - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 826 </DOCNO> The international companies using only English - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 827 </DOCNO> The child-free couples who treat their pets like children - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 828 </DOCNO> The people meeting the needs of India’s super-rich - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 829 </DOCNO> This is the most enterprising town in Britain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 830 </DOCNO> Why flats dominate Spain’s housing market - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 831 </DOCNO> The top reasons mothers are still leaving the workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 832 </DOCNO> Microbreaks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 833 </DOCNO> The rise of the multibillion-dollar corporate campus - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 834 </DOCNO> What will the world look like in the future? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 835 </DOCNO> How to be more efficient: stop ‘precrastinating’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 836 </DOCNO> FIRE: The movement to live frugally and retire decades early - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 837 </DOCNO> Why it’s a good thing to start Christmas in October - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 838 </DOCNO> Being depressed in the 'world's happiest country' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 839 </DOCNO> The city where you pay a year's rent up front - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 840 </DOCNO> Why this juice firm won’t squeeze its growers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 841 </DOCNO> The single mums who live together on ‘mommunes’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 842 </DOCNO> Inside the lives of Dubai’s ‘super rich’ kids - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 843 </DOCNO> How we could sleep better – in less time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 844 </DOCNO> Office Space turns 20: How the film changed the way we work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 845 </DOCNO> Microdosing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 846 </DOCNO> How to write emails in a pandemic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 847 </DOCNO> Why you shouldn't imitate Bill Gates if you want to be rich - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 848 </DOCNO> Kenya's changing population captured in 100 photos - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 849 </DOCNO> The trick to learning when to cut your losses - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 850 </DOCNO> Garages – the new affordable houses? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 851 </DOCNO> Britain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 852 </DOCNO> Why we should all give up on goals already - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 853 </DOCNO> Fred Swaniker - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 854 </DOCNO> Job Search - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 855 </DOCNO> The hidden air pollution inside your workplace - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 856 </DOCNO> The servants making $150,000 a year - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 857 </DOCNO> How ‘flow’ brings out your full potential - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 858 </DOCNO> Sweden’s surprising rule for time off - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 859 </DOCNO> Facial recognition - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 860 </DOCNO> Behavioural economics  - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 861 </DOCNO> This is where country club meets co-working space - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 862 </DOCNO> The firm outfitting the world’s armies - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 863 </DOCNO> What we just don't understand about the 1% - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 864 </DOCNO> This is what to do if you've been sacked - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 865 </DOCNO> Will this be the happiest place in the world? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 866 </DOCNO> Portfolio career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 867 </DOCNO> Why are flowers so expensive? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 868 </DOCNO> Why British beer is huge in China - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 869 </DOCNO> The great shrinking airline seat </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 870 </DOCNO> Interview abuse - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 871 </DOCNO> What if we have to work until we're 100? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 872 </DOCNO> Coronavirus: Will our day-to-day ever be the same? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 873 </DOCNO> Essentialism - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 874 </DOCNO> The never-ending battle over the best office temperature - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 875 </DOCNO> The surprising benefits of a reply-all email storm - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 876 </DOCNO> Unlike most millennials, Norway's are rich - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 877 </DOCNO> Why a boss-free office may not be as good as it sounds - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 878 </DOCNO> Hyperinflation is affecting how Venezuelans have sex - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 879 </DOCNO> Children of the Chinese super-rich aren’t all burning money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 880 </DOCNO> Millennials - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 881 </DOCNO> What would it take to become a trillionaire? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 882 </DOCNO> Idiosyncrasies of the Brits at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 883 </DOCNO> Why so many people fall for scams - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 884 </DOCNO> Why this coffee costs $75 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 885 </DOCNO> A ‘thrilling’ mission to get the Swedish to change overnight - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 886 </DOCNO> Executives - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 887 </DOCNO> Can’t find a job? Try this simple advice - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 888 </DOCNO> The world's most exclusive party - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 889 </DOCNO> How to induce sleep without drugs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 890 </DOCNO> Grit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 891 </DOCNO> For a happier home life, is bigger always better? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 892 </DOCNO> Third Culture Kids: Citizens of everywhere and nowhere - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 893 </DOCNO> How is extreme luxury defined? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 894 </DOCNO> Is this the sweet secret to Swedish success? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 895 </DOCNO> Thermostats - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 896 </DOCNO> Paranoid? It could be the key to your success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 897 </DOCNO> What cubicle dwellers want even more than money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 898 </DOCNO> In praise of micromanagement - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 899 </DOCNO> The threat of ‘globotics’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 900 </DOCNO> The secret to landing the best internships - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 901 </DOCNO> The cost of changing a country's name - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 902 </DOCNO> Popularity at work still matters whether we like it or not - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 903 </DOCNO> How expats cope with losing their identity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 904 </DOCNO> Why fans of vintage vinyl love this brand-new machine - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 905 </DOCNO> Is there a perfect time to look for a new job? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 906 </DOCNO> Want to change the world? Don’t look to Davos - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 907 </DOCNO> Cheesy? Yes. But here's how a reunion could get you a job - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 908 </DOCNO> How being a rebel at work gets you ahead - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 909 </DOCNO> How algorithms keep workers in the dark - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 910 </DOCNO> Libra - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 911 </DOCNO> Could we be facing a ‘chocapocalypse’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 912 </DOCNO> Should I quit? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 913 </DOCNO> A foreign affair: When expats date locals - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 914 </DOCNO> If your boss asked you to take a polygraph test, would you? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 915 </DOCNO> The problem with being a long-term expat - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 916 </DOCNO> Kkondae - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 917 </DOCNO> Surprising revelations from Davos - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 918 </DOCNO> Biohacking - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 919 </DOCNO> How carmakers brought new cuisine to Chennai - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 920 </DOCNO> What turns a product into a global phenomenon? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 921 </DOCNO> How to fake confidence - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 922 </DOCNO> Breakfast is the real power hour for success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 923 </DOCNO> Conscious Consumer - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 924 </DOCNO> The dating app built for young Egyptians - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 925 </DOCNO> Inside the high-pressure world of China’s start-up workers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 926 </DOCNO> Burnout - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 927 </DOCNO> Salary negotiations: Speak up or miss out - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 928 </DOCNO> This is why you should ‘advertise your ignorance’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 929 </DOCNO> Hate talking on the phone? This interview is for you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 930 </DOCNO> How avocados and kale became so popular - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 931 </DOCNO> Why you’re afraid to share your opinions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 932 </DOCNO> Why paying for pandas is not so black and white - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 933 </DOCNO> The country trying to make all its people happier - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 934 </DOCNO> The 'smart' baby technology raising today's children - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 935 </DOCNO> Why is Sweden deporting talented tech workers? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 936 </DOCNO> Platform co-operatives - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 937 </DOCNO> Make a move: Changing track mid-career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 938 </DOCNO> Schmoozing like a winner: A guide to networking Davos-style - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 939 </DOCNO> If your boss is a lifer, consider this before you quit - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 940 </DOCNO> Where are all the unused planes right now? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 941 </DOCNO> Drugs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 942 </DOCNO> How Greece is reversing brain drain - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 943 </DOCNO> Spanish millennials are reshaping their goals to afford life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 944 </DOCNO> The surprising benefits – and risks – of trash talk - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 945 </DOCNO> Why you might be missing your commute - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 946 </DOCNO> Will we all soon be using ‘biometric CVs’? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 947 </DOCNO> These are the surprising connections between the Davos elite - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 948 </DOCNO> How the Black Death made the rich richer - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 949 </DOCNO> Instead of the pub after work, they get naked together here - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 950 </DOCNO> The changing perks of a pseudonym - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 951 </DOCNO> What’s your app — Davos edition - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 952 </DOCNO> Breathable offices - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 953 </DOCNO> Should I delete Tinder? These millennials think so - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 954 </DOCNO> Expats in paradise - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 955 </DOCNO> What will millennials kill this year? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 956 </DOCNO> The bizarre rise of fast food fused with snack foods - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 957 </DOCNO> Managers: Train your brain for ethical decisions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 958 </DOCNO> The 'extra something special' employers seek - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 959 </DOCNO> The danger of overusing exclamation marks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 960 </DOCNO> What’s behind the rise in cannabis-infused products? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 961 </DOCNO> Hidden disabilities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 962 </DOCNO> Climate change: What Davos execs say is next - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 963 </DOCNO> The big problem with short queues - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 964 </DOCNO> How a Twitter clone heralded a no-code boom - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 965 </DOCNO> Social Media - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 966 </DOCNO> People have always whinged about young adults. Here's proof - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 967 </DOCNO> Are nervous habits derailing your job interview? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 968 </DOCNO> Is upscale expat life in Geneva worth your money? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 969 </DOCNO> How shark attacks became big business for Australia - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 970 </DOCNO> Can technology help you lose an accent? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 971 </DOCNO> Permalancing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 972 </DOCNO> Ethics - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 973 </DOCNO> Do screen time rules still apply in lockdown? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 974 </DOCNO> Why expats call this utopia - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 975 </DOCNO> The CEO with no home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 976 </DOCNO> A Davos journey in pictures - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 977 </DOCNO> Lifting the lid on Japan’s amazing bento boxes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 978 </DOCNO> The unfair stigma surrounding millennials and their money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 979 </DOCNO> The new way your personality could be holding you back - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 980 </DOCNO> The Swedes ditching desks to work from strangers’ homes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 981 </DOCNO> Humble leadership - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 982 </DOCNO> Simpler spelling may be more relevant than ever - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 983 </DOCNO> Grey nomads: Australia’s roving retirees - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 984 </DOCNO> Bright Sparks - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 985 </DOCNO> Inclusion workshops - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 986 </DOCNO> The one writing skill you must master - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 987 </DOCNO> Bangkok shouldn’t be good for expats – but it is - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 988 </DOCNO> Why women should interrupt men - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 989 </DOCNO> How do you make friends in a new country? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 990 </DOCNO> Boss’s mistake — but your head on the line - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 991 </DOCNO> Knocked down? How easily will you get back up? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 992 </DOCNO> The peculiar psychoanalysis of job hiring - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 993 </DOCNO> How a once taboo topic came out from the shadows at Davos - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 994 </DOCNO> ASMR: The big business of making super soft sounds - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 995 </DOCNO> Why business cards still matter - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 996 </DOCNO> German dorms are so pricey, students are building their own - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 997 </DOCNO> Crowdfunding - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 998 </DOCNO> The high price of this beachside paradise - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 999 </DOCNO> The beautiful ways different cultures sign emails - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1000 </DOCNO> What is BBC Worklife? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1001 </DOCNO> Stop texting your money away - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1002 </DOCNO> The tiny flats taking over Latin America - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1003 </DOCNO> Looking for your dream job? Swipe right - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1004 </DOCNO> New Economy Entrepreneurs  - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1005 </DOCNO> This is where the real deals at Davos are done - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1006 </DOCNO> Karoshi - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1007 </DOCNO> Should you change your name to get a job? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1008 </DOCNO> China's rebel generation and the rise of 'hot words' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1009 </DOCNO> Corporate credit card, personal expenses - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1010 </DOCNO> Introverted? Here are the jobs for you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1011 </DOCNO> How communal-living groups are riding out the pandemic - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1012 </DOCNO> A new way to teach English - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1013 </DOCNO> What would you really like to say with your 'out-of-office'? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1014 </DOCNO> A booming city with a brutal history - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1015 </DOCNO> Scared of the phone? Here's how to overcome that fear - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1016 </DOCNO> 5G internet - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1017 </DOCNO> If you get rich, you won’t quit working for long - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1018 </DOCNO> 'I hadn't been home for three years': One migrant's struggle - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1019 </DOCNO> The art of dealing with difficult people at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1020 </DOCNO> Noise pollution - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1021 </DOCNO> Making a six-figure sum in a single weekend - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1022 </DOCNO> How two iPads and a smartphone became the new normal - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1023 </DOCNO> The rise of the Twitch-preneurs and the evolution of tipping - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1024 </DOCNO> In-the-office days - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1025 </DOCNO> How memes got broke millennials through the recession - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1026 </DOCNO> Why less is much, much more on LinkedIn - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1027 </DOCNO> A tiny nation that can boost expat careers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1028 </DOCNO> How to speak like a champion — literally - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1029 </DOCNO> The challenges of positive parenting - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1030 </DOCNO> The housing project where young and old must mingle - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1031 </DOCNO> Who should be able to afford 'affordable' housing? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1032 </DOCNO> US women’s football team - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1033 </DOCNO> What monkeys can teach us about money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1034 </DOCNO> The taxi driver who brings her toddler to work every night - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1035 </DOCNO> Where will all the workers go? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1036 </DOCNO> Autocomplete - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1037 </DOCNO> Anti-distraction apps - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1038 </DOCNO> Say what? When the boss is a gossip - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1039 </DOCNO> The best CEOs of 2013 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1040 </DOCNO> Coping with grief — and funeral costs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1041 </DOCNO> Which generation owns Kazakstan’s future? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1042 </DOCNO> Buzzword bingo, Davos edition - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1043 </DOCNO> Is this China’s best city for expats? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1044 </DOCNO> Management mistakes — and opportunities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1045 </DOCNO> This 13-year-old makes apps to teach others about his autism - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1046 </DOCNO> The major cities being designed without children in mind - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1047 </DOCNO> Humanics - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1048 </DOCNO> The gruelling, six-hour commute of Beijing’s workers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1049 </DOCNO> Leaveism - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1050 </DOCNO> The surprising benefits of living beyond your means - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1051 </DOCNO> Welcome to the Family Values series - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1052 </DOCNO> Gaming - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1053 </DOCNO> The worst CEOs of 2013 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1054 </DOCNO> Is workplace rudeness on the rise? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1055 </DOCNO> Happiness coaches - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1056 </DOCNO> Even desert city Dubai imports its sand. This is why - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1057 </DOCNO> An unpredictable expat locale - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1058 </DOCNO> The Zambian agri-tech app making farming cool - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1059 </DOCNO> Reverse mentoring - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1060 </DOCNO> Toys of the rich — better than yours - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1061 </DOCNO> The apps combatting 'sharenting' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1062 </DOCNO> ‘I’ve changed outfits 485 times in a single day’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1063 </DOCNO> China’s first global luxury brand - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1064 </DOCNO> Is this the world’s most liveable city? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1065 </DOCNO> The ‘minterns’ taking internships in their 30s - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1066 </DOCNO> Remote workforce - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1067 </DOCNO> Middle East - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1068 </DOCNO> How to turn coffee love into a career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1069 </DOCNO> In deprived areas, depression hits men harder - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1070 </DOCNO> Family ties - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1071 </DOCNO> Did Disney shape how you see the world? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1072 </DOCNO> When the ‘wrong’ thing at work is surprisingly right - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1073 </DOCNO> The ‘light-bringers’ of sub-Saharan Africa - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1074 </DOCNO> Adaptability quotient - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1075 </DOCNO> Inside Beijing’s immense, fantastical wedding photo studio - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1076 </DOCNO> Where's your loyalty: your boss or your team? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1077 </DOCNO> Can “Made in China” become a luxury label? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1078 </DOCNO> A history of avoiding distractions </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1079 </DOCNO> Degrowth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1080 </DOCNO> Beyond fun, when being a gamer turns into a lucrative career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1081 </DOCNO> Can 'phone booths' solve the problem of open-plan offices? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1082 </DOCNO> Private jet travel gets the Uber treatment - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1083 </DOCNO> The workplaces that will pay for surrogacy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1084 </DOCNO> Playing the confidence game at work — the wrong way - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1085 </DOCNO> Telepresence - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1086 </DOCNO> The man helping millions of Chinese find their voice - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1087 </DOCNO> Charitable dilemma:  The pitfalls of a nonprofit board seat - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1088 </DOCNO> The subtle design tricks that help – and harm – creativity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1089 </DOCNO> I reported the boss to HR — now what? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1090 </DOCNO> How to leave a family business - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1091 </DOCNO> How chronic renters are reshaping the homeware industry - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1092 </DOCNO> Why Japan’s ‘shūkatsu’ job-seeking system is changing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1093 </DOCNO> The end of Apple as we know it? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1094 </DOCNO> The man who built his own floating home - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1095 </DOCNO> Ghosting at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1096 </DOCNO> The health hacks of elite travellers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1097 </DOCNO> The gin renaissance sweeping across Europe - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1098 </DOCNO> Should you fire or help an employee with a drug addiction? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1099 </DOCNO> Squads - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1100 </DOCNO> How your parents may have shaped the way you act at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1101 </DOCNO> When office gossip is about you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1102 </DOCNO> Picking the next Chinese start-up star - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1103 </DOCNO> The CEOs who don't feel successful - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1104 </DOCNO> A fatal flaw when choosing the right leader - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1105 </DOCNO> Smart offices - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1106 </DOCNO> The We Company - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1107 </DOCNO> The camp that makes future millionaires - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1108 </DOCNO> The flight routines of super-travellers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1109 </DOCNO> How Muslim headscarves became a fashion empire - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1110 </DOCNO> Why sleeping in could make you a better worker - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1111 </DOCNO> Sleep - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1112 </DOCNO> Should kids financially support their parents? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1113 </DOCNO> Can social media get you fired? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1114 </DOCNO> Will they get what they came for? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1115 </DOCNO> When a question becomes a chance to show off - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1116 </DOCNO> Liz Johnson - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1117 </DOCNO> Secrets of the world’s top CEOs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1118 </DOCNO> Slack - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1119 </DOCNO> Don’t say this at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1120 </DOCNO> This man gets paid to write hashtags - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1121 </DOCNO> The story behind one charity CEO’s Davos ambitions - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1122 </DOCNO> The five must–have leadership traits - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1123 </DOCNO> Is 'platonic parenting' the relationship of the future? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1124 </DOCNO> 'Girl boss': When empowerment slogans backfire - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1125 </DOCNO> FIRE movement - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1126 </DOCNO> Four ways to train your brain to cope with heavy travel - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1127 </DOCNO> Level Up  - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1128 </DOCNO> e-Residency - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1129 </DOCNO> Bonus time: Why it’s still a man’s world - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1130 </DOCNO> Why overtired Japan is turning to office siestas - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1131 </DOCNO> A pilot’s story: Flying high, at home and at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1132 </DOCNO> Cut the cord but keep your favourite programmes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1133 </DOCNO> The story of Coke's rise on the Gaza Strip - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1134 </DOCNO> This is the humblebrag that could sink you - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1135 </DOCNO> How coronavirus has transformed the way we communicate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1136 </DOCNO> Real Estate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1137 </DOCNO> Office farming - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1138 </DOCNO> The words you never want to hear at a job interview - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1139 </DOCNO> The power of inspiration - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1140 </DOCNO> The entourages of the travel elite - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1141 </DOCNO> Nanoinfluencers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1142 </DOCNO> The problem with abolishing coins - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1143 </DOCNO> Davos2016 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1144 </DOCNO> Could this be the end of the true panama hat? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1145 </DOCNO> What does it really take to stop wasting time? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1146 </DOCNO> Will TikTok stars ever make money? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1147 </DOCNO> Pay transparency - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1148 </DOCNO> Young, female and forging ahead in Gaza - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1149 </DOCNO> The fixers for the high-flying elite - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1150 </DOCNO> How to be a great boss — and leave on time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1151 </DOCNO> Smart strategies to avoid a bad hire - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1152 </DOCNO> The downside of being nice at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1153 </DOCNO> Radical candour - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1154 </DOCNO> The man who makes six figures rating dogs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1155 </DOCNO> 100-year lifespan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1156 </DOCNO> Nine things you need to know so you can profit from property - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1157 </DOCNO> Meet the people with almost nothing in their closets - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1158 </DOCNO> Why a side hustle may be more important for women than men - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1159 </DOCNO> Secrets to saving on renovations - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1160 </DOCNO> Why 3D is more than a passing fad for jobs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1161 </DOCNO> The downsides of being rich - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1162 </DOCNO> Automated hiring and firing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1163 </DOCNO> Secrets of getting good sleep on a plane - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1164 </DOCNO> Here’s proof that mum really did know best - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1165 </DOCNO> Meet the boss who works in three continents - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1166 </DOCNO> Mariéme Jamme - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1167 </DOCNO> The right way to get noticed in your career - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1168 </DOCNO> The hidden beat makers behind music’s big hits - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1169 </DOCNO> Capital Video - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1170 </DOCNO> Spinning gold from tall tales in Bangladesh - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1171 </DOCNO> Fashion - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1172 </DOCNO> Finance vests - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1173 </DOCNO> The retirees who room with refugees - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1174 </DOCNO> When personal and professional lives collide - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1175 </DOCNO> Loneliness often follows sudden wealth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1176 </DOCNO> Superjobs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1177 </DOCNO> Expat culture shock boomerangs in the office - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1178 </DOCNO> Run out of time to use your leave days – again? Do this. - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1179 </DOCNO> Non-binary acceptance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1180 </DOCNO> Yes, you can retire at 40 - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1181 </DOCNO> Post-work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1182 </DOCNO> You can teach yourself to be a risk-taker - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1183 </DOCNO> Meet the man behind Google’s doodles - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1184 </DOCNO> The secret to stopping your ‘ummms’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1185 </DOCNO> To find success, Arab women go west - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1186 </DOCNO> This is what the best bosses are really made of - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1187 </DOCNO> Making big money out of a fashion dilemma - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1188 </DOCNO> Why promoted women are more likely to divorce - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1189 </DOCNO> Why this green stone can be worth more than gold - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1190 </DOCNO> The harsh lessons of your twenties - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1191 </DOCNO> Soft skills - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1192 </DOCNO> India’s sweet tooth turns to artisanal chocolate - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1193 </DOCNO> The case for an entirely new calendar - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1194 </DOCNO> Couple inequity - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1195 </DOCNO> This is how to really make money from student life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1196 </DOCNO> The art of confronting unethical client activities - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1197 </DOCNO> Asia’s overlooked business dynamo - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1198 </DOCNO> This is how to tackle your bucket list - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1199 </DOCNO> Adapting to Dubai’s change of pace during Ramadan - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1200 </DOCNO> Co-living - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1201 </DOCNO> Here's the real reason you don't fit in at work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1202 </DOCNO> How to find a job with no Sunday night blues - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1203 </DOCNO> Why a side-gig can be harder for women - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1204 </DOCNO> Algorithmic justice - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1205 </DOCNO> Four ways paid paternity leave could boost family income - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1206 </DOCNO> More than a tropical Shangri-la - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1207 </DOCNO> Why these three questions can solve any problem - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1208 </DOCNO> Hirune - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1209 </DOCNO> India - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1210 </DOCNO> Investing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1211 </DOCNO> Return of ‘airpocalypse’: Beijing’s expats flee smog - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1212 </DOCNO> Say goodbye to sexism in the office, for real this time - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1213 </DOCNO> How to create something everyone wants - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1214 </DOCNO> Could you afford to be a stay-at-home parent? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1215 </DOCNO> Why all eyes are turning to this Aussie city - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1216 </DOCNO> Forget retirement, your grandchildren need you to raise them - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1217 </DOCNO> Mia Perdomo and Andrea de la Piedra - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1218 </DOCNO> The people getting rich off the discards of our addiction - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1219 </DOCNO> Unretirement - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1220 </DOCNO> We can learn a lot from how the French do lunch - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1221 </DOCNO> Denmark’s state-funded ‘hotels’ for new mums - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1222 </DOCNO> Beijing bound: Jobs hot spot for expats? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1223 </DOCNO> Universal basic income - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1224 </DOCNO> The trouble with invisible success - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1225 </DOCNO> Why we love these relics - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1226 </DOCNO> Alternative workspaces: Turning your home into a breadwinner - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1227 </DOCNO> Lifehack - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1228 </DOCNO> Family - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1229 </DOCNO> The world’s most influential shoppers - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1230 </DOCNO> Should you ever push products onto your friends? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1231 </DOCNO> Shopify - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1232 </DOCNO> Facing death, new perspective on work and life - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1233 </DOCNO> Three traits that will get you hired by the best bosses - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1234 </DOCNO> Want to become an Australian? Jump through these hoops - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1235 </DOCNO> Why daughters might be better than sons - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1236 </DOCNO> The end of the inbox: Companies that banned email - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1237 </DOCNO> This is what CEOs are most worried about - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1238 </DOCNO> Your love for toy trains could bring more than joy - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1239 </DOCNO> Freddy Vega - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1240 </DOCNO> Keys to The Kingdom: The slow rise of Saudi women - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1241 </DOCNO> Will an expensive degree boost your career? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1242 </DOCNO> The woman who lifted a village </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1243 </DOCNO> Inside China's extreme wedding craze - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1244 </DOCNO> How China spent $1 billion in eight minutes - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1245 </DOCNO> Smart ways to get Harvard on your CV - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1246 </DOCNO> Where are all the expat women? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1247 </DOCNO> Why working from home could be bad for your health - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1248 </DOCNO> Gig reality - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1249 </DOCNO> Master the art of global email etiquette - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1250 </DOCNO> Worklife - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1251 </DOCNO> Birth - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1252 </DOCNO> Smart money advice, from poker playing cowboys? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1253 </DOCNO> All that glitters: Brutal climate, shiny payday - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1254 </DOCNO> Would you commute by plane for a good job? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1255 </DOCNO> Meet Canada’s ‘weed sommelier’ - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1256 </DOCNO> Inside the world of super-rare car investing - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1257 </DOCNO> The women who empty their savings to freeze their eggs - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1258 </DOCNO> Hyper-surveillance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1259 </DOCNO> Bees do it, so why can’t bee keepers and colleagues? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1260 </DOCNO> Bizarre job interviews, exposed - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1261 </DOCNO> Why working dads don’t talk about balance - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1262 </DOCNO> Hate open floor office spaces? There’s a better way. - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1263 </DOCNO> This 13-year-old helps kids around the world learn languages - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1264 </DOCNO> The secretive world of 'danger pay' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1265 </DOCNO> Rebuilding lives — and livelihoods — after war - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1266 </DOCNO> Step aside Paris Hilton, here’s how to own hotels - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1267 </DOCNO> The weddings designed with Instagram in mind - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1268 </DOCNO> A spender marries a saver — now what? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1269 </DOCNO> Your handshake around the world - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1270 </DOCNO> Why 2.3 million people wanted this job - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1271 </DOCNO> Eight dismissals that made headlines - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1272 </DOCNO> When texting goes corporate, skip the 'LOL' - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1273 </DOCNO> What will Australian workers do next? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1274 </DOCNO> How to fake a shopping buzz without spending any money - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1275 </DOCNO> Is the time ripe to buy Middle Eastern art? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1276 </DOCNO> How the second time around can pay off big - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1277 </DOCNO> Deep work - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1278 </DOCNO> Uganda’s life-threatening ‘boda boda’ commute - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1279 </DOCNO> Is this the real liquid gold? - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1280 </DOCNO> You may be tempted to leave this off your CV. Don’t - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1281 </DOCNO> Want the job? First you'll have to meet the wife - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1282 </DOCNO> The secrets of success in India - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1283 </DOCNO> Tales from Modern China - BBC Worklife </DOC>
<DOC> <DOCNO> 1284 </DOCNO> Why you don'